<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[www.barrymutch.com]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[www.barrymutch.com]]></description>
        <link>http://barrymutch.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 17:08:58 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://barrymutch.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/45693943-404c-4a29-a44e-aa8ea408e6c1.jpg">,<p>I am here…Switzerland….For one purpose.</p>,<p>To record my debut album a lifetime in the making.</p>,<p>I have come a long way to a peaceful place and I have brought with me, through great trials and tribulations , the tools of the trade, the teeth, do. to speak to make it happen.</p>,<p>I am asking for those of you that believe in the arts for something that I believe is an equal trade at best.</p>,<p>In exchange for 13 CHF i promise to deliver to you 13 songs recorded st the highest quality and chosen from a lifetime of songwriting, songs that I believe sit well together and deliver a message that is much needed right now.</p>,<p>Songs of hope and unity.</p>,<p>I have written many types of songs for other artists.</p>,<p>I have produced and engineered songs for other artists but I have never sat down and out together a message from me to this volatile and frail world that speaks from my own heart directly.</p>,<p>I hope that you will find it in yourself to take a small risk and see if what I have to share is worth considering.</p>,<p>i wish for connection. For commonality. For understanding.</p>,<p>Maybe not total peace but a little love.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://barrymutch.com/i-am-hereswitzerlandfor-one-purpose/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">93ddac30-e4cb-4a0c-b4d7-582df753c6d0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2017 17:08:49 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>